Soon,
you won't even need
the Roblox app to
play Roblox.
This is ViralRoblox
news.
At RDC,
Roblox's yearly developer conference,
Roblox announced a web
player.
By the end of
this year,
you'll be able to
join games in your
browser on Chrome.
No app,
no install,
more browsers are coming
later,
and it all starts
with a link.
Search,
YouTube,
X,
even an email from
a friend.
Click it and you
start playing instantly.
That's not all.
Offline play is coming
too.
Game creators will be
able to add solo
modes that work with
no internet.
On a plane,
on the train,
anywhere.
That's planned for mid-2027,
with early access coming
soon.
So what does this
mean for you?
Got a friend who's
never played Roblox?
Soon,
all they'll need is
one link.
Follow ViralRobloxGames
so you never miss
Roblox news.
Would you play Roblox
in your browser or
stick with the app?
Comment below.
I'm Skye,
this has been ViralRoblox
News.
Follow for more.